onedaykorea.com 2016-04-30

# Privacy Policy for Korea Travelers by One Day Korea

You are here: [Home](http://www.onedaykorea.com/) / Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We see you as a valuable asset that we want to protect and safeguard. To show you our commitment, we have compiled this Privacy Policy page. It outlines everything our company does all the time to safeguard your privacy on this website. We reserve the right to add new services or features to this Privacy Policy in future. Kindly read it thoroughly.

**Note: From this point on our website, www.onedaykorea.com, will be referred to as One Day Korea, our, us or we.**

**1.Usage**

You agree to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy each time you view our website.  
One Day Korea wants to use this Privacy Policy to let you know more about our rules and regulations on information handling. All the data we collect from our customers will be subject to these rules and regulations. They stipulate how personal data will be gathered, managed, used, stored, transferred or disclosed.  
This Privacy Policy affects only that information you have shared with us through www.onedaykorea.com or via our mobile application. We keep the right to occasionally alter sections of this Privacy Policy to reflect changes we have made to our company. Needless to say, changes will reflect on our website immediately and each user will be notified by email.

**2\. Information gathering and Use.**

We gather information to boost our service delivery and platform  
We would like to point out that the only reason why we collect your personal information is to improve this platform. We want you to access One Day Korea services, applications, features and other things with ease.

**3\. Personal identification data**

We need your most basic personal identification data to re-model our services to suit your needs.  
When you surf our website without signing up, you remain unknown to us. However, if you decide to sign up with us through www.onedaykorea.com or our mobile application, we capture your personal information.  
We become curious to know you when you show interest in becoming our event host, traveler or just a member. Our system must collect your personal identification data just incase we need to get in touch with you. We consider personal information to entail, but not limited to the following: name, phone number, house number and email address.  
At this point we do not need your billing information, date of birth…etc. But if you sign up with us we assume that you have agreed to let your identity details be entered on our computers/servers. If you will become an event host we have the right to require confirmation of your personal identification data like your physical address.  
We do use personal but non-indentifying data to customize your One Day Korea account profile. But when we want to use your private data to improve our site and its services, we use both identifying and non-identifying information.  
For instance, we may use it to send you newsletters and other promotional data. If you do not want to receive our frequent updates you can unsubscribe.

**4\. Browser generated data**

We use browser data or log data collected when you are browsing our site to maximize our site.  
Log data is automatically recorded by browsers whenever you visit different websites. When you visit our website via your browser, our servers will pick up your log data. It will contain your computer’s Internet Protocol address, ISP data, language, date or time of your visit, previously visited page, pages visited on our site, time you took on each page, what you clicked on, and how often you visit us. We do not use this data in any other way except to enhance our services.

**5\. Cookies**

One Day Korea uses Cookies to gather information  
A cookie is just a tiny data file that is kept on your computer’s drive and it can be removed. We utilize cookies to store personal information for easier retrieval when our experts are revamping the site and its properties. If you do not want our cookies you may alter your browser settings.

**6\. Registration is mandatory.**

To host an event or book an event you must join us via registration.  
In order to have your listing accepted and displayed on One Day Korea site, we need your personal information first. The same case applies to travelers who expect to book an event via our site. Listings published by event hosts, reviews of both travelers and event hosts and their profile information will be shown to all registered and non-registered users of One Day Korea.  
So, when you accept to join us via our site, you are letting us set up a profile page that will reflect what you are selling. Your account profile page will indicate your first and last name. If you wish to add a photograph or links to the services you are offering, you should let us know.  
Besides showing your profile page to site users, we may show it on third party sites (but only with your permission). We give you the right to alter your profile information at any time.

**7\. Third parties**

We will share information with third parties when necessary  
Although we share data for planning purposes, we will never let out your personal identification information. Third parties can access our servers by request though. For instance, if we need their technical support on our site, such as have them do website or mobile application repairs, detect fraud, manage our database or perform web analytics, third parties will access your personal information. However, third parties are also bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**8\. Observing the law**

We may reveal personal identification data if the law of your country demands it.  
We cannot refuse the public authorities or the government entities your personal information if it is required for a court process or any other use. If we discover that your personal data is unethical, illegal or dangerous to national security, we will be forced to reveal it. In order to insure One Day Korea properties, including you, we may reveal your personal details to our insurers.

**9.Altering, Selling or sharing information**

You reserve the right to alter your personal information  
One Day Korea could transfer, sell or share all or part of its asset portfolios, including your personal data, if it were to form a merger, an acquisition or undergo a restructuring process of any kind due to bankruptcy or disposal of assets.  
If you want to cease being our member, you may contact us to delete/cancel your account and we will delete it if we do not have any reasons to avoid it. Note that while you are gone any reviews you may have written or received will stay publicly viewable on the site.

**10.Data security**

Your data safety is our top priority.  
We take serious and stern measures to hide and mask your personal information from prying eyes. Our servers are totally encrypted with the SSL or Secure Socket Layer technology. This technology plays the role of hiding data as it gets transmitted over the internet. Still we advise you to think carefully when deciding what to add to your account profile page. Should you have security concerns or questions, let us know.

__
